Today, we are going to learn how to make gourmet coffee in your home.
In this clip, we're going to be talking a little about the coffee that we actually use, the grind of it, and what kind of roast we're going to use to get the best shots of espresso.
If you're using an espresso machine, you're going to want to use like a finer grind of coffee.
To change the amount or the time that your espresso shots are going to take, you're going to do a thicker or a finer grind.
Finer grind is going to be less time on the shots.
A thicker grind is going to let the water sipped in a little bit more and take a longer time to pull the shots.
Now, we're using a fine grind right now which is great for us because we're pulling these great shots of espresso.
And with espresso, the finer the grind, the better the shots that we make.
Also, you want to be very aware of what kind of beans you're using.
I mentioned earlier that you don't want to use like a cheap auto-drip whatever coffee beans to make your espresso shots.
What you do want to use though is a rich, good coffee.
You can get a lot of just good coffees at your local grocery store, and if you have an espresso grinder that's even better.
So what you're going to do is turn to a finer grind.
You're going to grind it and then you're going to be able to pull the shots.